Guide to the School of Medicine, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Deans George Blumer, Milton C. Winternitz, Stanhope Bayne-Jones, Francis G. Blake, and Cyril N. H. Long, 1888-1960; Accession 1961-A-002
  - General Correspondence
    - Taffel, Max, 1937 (Box 98, Folder 2303)
    - Taft, Priscilla Dienes, 1944 (Box 98, Folder 2304)
    - Taft, William Howard, 1914 (Box 98, Folder 2305)
    - Tamara, Thomas Henry, 1922 (Box 98, Folder 2306)
    - Tennant, Robert, 1941 (Box 98, Folder 2307)
    - Terhlme, W. B., 1926-1931 (Box 98, Folder 2308)
    - Thacher,. Henry C., 1919 (Box 98, Folder 2309)
    - Thayer, W.S., 1923 (Box 98, Folder 2310)
    - Thom, Douglas A., 1926-1927 (Box 98, Folder 2311)
    - Thompson, Kenneth W., 1935-1938 (Box 98, Folder 2312)
    - Tilney, Frederick, 1940 (Box 98, Folder 2313)
    - Titus, Paul, 1938 (Box 98, Folder 2314)
    - Townsend, Joseph H., 1910-15 (Box 98, Folder 2315)
    - Tso, Ernest, 1926 (Box 98, Folder 2316)
    - Twaddle, Paul Holmes, 1935 (Box 98, Folder 2317)
    - U miscellaneous, 1935-1952 (Box 98, Folder 2318 - 2319)
    - Ussher, Neville., 1933 (Box 98, Folder 2320)
    - V general, 1933-1954 (Box 98, Folder 2321)
    - V miscellaneous, 1930-1942 (Box 98, Folder 2322 - 2323)
    - Van Allen, Chester, 1930 (Box 98, Folder 2324)
    - Vandegrift, William B., 1937 (Box 98, Folder 2325)
    - Vaughn, Martha, 1949 (Box 98, Folder 2326)
    - W general, 1918-1944 (Box 98, Folder 2327 - 2328)
    - VI miscellaneous, 1930-1952 (Box 98, Folder 2329 - 2330)
    - Wagner, Carl P., 1930 (Box 99, Folder 2331)
    - Hain, Harry, 1942 (Box 99, Folder 2332)
    - Waite, Frederic C.: Western Reserve University, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 2333)
    - Wakeman, A. Maurice, 1921-1932 (Box 99, Folder 2334)
    - Walker, W. Bradford, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 2335)
    - Waring, T.P., 1939 (Box 99, Folder 2336)
    - Warren, Charles H., 1933 (Box 99, Folder 2337)
    - Waterman, Dr. Paul, 1922 (Box 99, Folder 2339)
    - Waugh, Theodore R., 1939 (Box 99, Folder 2340)
    - Wear., Joseph H.: Philadelphia; Pa., 1930 (Box 99, Folder 2341)
    - Weed, Lewis H., 1928-1945 (Box 99, Folder 2342)
    - Weiner, Abraham, 1925 (Box 99, Folder 2343)
    - Weinstein, Louis, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 2344)
    - Weisberger, David, 1932 (Box 99, Folder 2345)
    - Welch, William H., 1925-1932 (Box 99, Folder 2346)
    - Whipple, George N., 1923 (Box 99, Folder 2347)
    - Whipple, Sherman L., 1929-1930 (Box 99, Folder 2348)
    - Whitney, Eli, 1925 (Box 99, Folder 2349)
    - Wiersma, E.D. (Sr.), Wiersma, D. (Son)., 1929-1933 (Box 99, Folder 2350)
    - Wiggin and Pana (Law Firm - Formerly called Bristol and White), 1934-1935 (Box 99, Folder 2351)
    - Wilens, Gustav, 1921 (Box 99, Folder 2352)
    - Williams, Frankwood E., 1926-1927 (Box 99, Folder 2353)
    - Williams, St. John, 1919 (Box 99, Folder 2354)
    - Wilson, George., 1926-1938 (Box 99, Folder 2355)
    - Wilson, George C., 1934 (Box 99, Folder 2356)
    - Winternitz, Milton C., 1920-1935 (Box 99, Folder 2357 - 2363)
    - Winternitz, Milton C., 1929-1941 (Box 100, Folder 2364 - 2367)
    - And Embree, E. R., 1928-1930. (Box 100, Folder 2368)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence as Pathologist rather-than Dean, 1922-1935 (Box 100, Folder 2369 - 2370)
    - Wolfish, Martin (Anatomy), 1949-1950 (Box 100, Folder 2371)
    - Wong, Cora, 1926 (Box 100, Folder 2372)
    - Woodruff, C. Eugene, 1926 (Box 100, Folder 2373)
    - Wyeth and Brother: Latin American Externe, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 2374)
    - X, Y, Z miscellaneous, 1935-1952 (Box 100, Folder 2375 - 2376)
    - Y general, 1924-1937 (Box 100, Folder 2377)
    - Yale Alumni Weekly, 1929-1932 (Box 100, Folder 2378)
    - Yale News, 1929-1931 (Box 100, Folder 2379)
    - Yale Scientific Magazine, 1929-1932 (Box 100, Folder 2380)
    - Yates, J.L., 1923-1924 (Box 100, Folder 2381)
    - Yen, F.C., 1938-1940 (Box 100, Folder 2382)
    - Young, I. Maureen, 1949-1950 (Box 100, Folder 2383)
    - Young, Thomas H., undated (Box 100, Folder 2385)
    - Yudkin, Arthur M., 1935 (Box 100, Folder 2386)
    - Z general, 1928-1933 (Box 100, Folder 2387)
    - Zinsser, Hans, 1924 (Box 100, Folder 2388)
    - Unidentified Correspondence, 1919-1952 (Box 100, Folder 2389)
  - General Education Board, 1924-1930 (Box 100, Folder 2390)
  - Graduation, 1943-1945 (Box 100, Folder 2391)
  - Health Insurance, 1915-19 (Box 101, Folder 2392)
  - Health Service Plan, 1930-1947 (Box 101, Folder 2393 - 2401)
  - Health Service Plan, 1942-1952 (Box 102, Folder 2402 - 2403)
    - Data, 1930 (Box 102, Folder 2404)
    - Memoranda, 1930 (Box 102, Folder 2405)
    - University Faculty, 1930 (Box 102, Folder 2406)
  - Histological Technique, 1929-1932 (Box 102, Folder 2407)
  - Historical, 1915-1952 (Box 102, Folder 2408 - 2409)
  - Historical Data, 1898-1906 (Box 102, Folder 2410)
    - School of Medicine, 1933-1934 (Box 102, Folder 2411)
  - Honor System, 1894-1912 (Box 102, Folder 2412)
  - Honor Degrees, 1929-1950 (Box 102, Folder 2413 - 2414)
  - Hospital, New Haven, 1914-1940 (Box 102, Folder 2415 - 2419)
  - Hospital, New Haven, 1927-1947 (Box 103, Folder 2420 - 2430)
    - Board of Directors, 1918-1927 (Box 103, Folder 2431 - 2432)
    - Board of Directors, 1928-1935 (Box 104, Folder 2433 - 2438)
    - Board of Directors, 1937-1940 (Box 105, Folder 2439 - 2442)
    - Application to Federal Emergency Administration, 1932-1933 (Box 105, Folder 2443)
    - Brady Laboratory, 1915-18 (Box 105, Folder 2444)
    - Building and Maintenance Department Proposed School of Medicine, 1928 (Box 105, Folder 2445)
    - Building Program, 1933 (Box 105, Folder 2446)
    - Centennial Celebration, 1926 (Box 105, Folder 2447)
    - Clinical Funds Collection, 1916-19 (Box 105, Folder 2448)
    - Construction, 1930-1931 (Box 105, Folder 2449)
    - Construction Plans, 1930 (Box 105, Folder 2450)
    - Construction Program, 1930 (Box 105, Folder 2451)
    - Construction Program.: Further Units, Private Pavilion, etc., 1913-1929 (Box 105, Folder 2452)
    - Costs, 1930-1938 (Box 105, Folder 2453 - 2455)
    - Costs and City Payments - Four Connecticut Cities, 1928-1934 (Box 105, Folder 2456)
    - Cost of Hospitalization, 1930-1934. (Box 105, Folder 2457)
    - Costs of Medical Care, 1932-1935 (Box 105, Folder 2458)
    - Costs of Medical Care - City Rate Case, 1932 (Box 105, Folder 2459)
    - Defense Program, 1932-1933 (Box 105, Folder 2460)
    - Dietitians, 1942 (Box 105, Folder 2461)
    - Directors, 1919-1920 (Box 105, Folder 2462)
    - Directors and Human Welfare Group Executive Committee, 1931 (Box 105, Folder 2463)
    - Directors' Meetings, 1934-1935 (Box 105, Folder 2464)
    - Directors' Reports of Visits, 1931 (Box 105, Folder 2465)
    - Dispensary, 1895-1918 (Box 105, Folder 2466 - 2467)
    - Dispensary, 1920-1939 (Box 106, Folder 2468 - 2472)
      - Social Service Department, 1913-1940 (Box 106, Folder 2473 - 2478)
    - Drive for Funds, Committee on, 1919 (Box 106, Folder 2479)
    - E.E.G. Laboratory, 1945-1948 (Box 106, Folder 2480)
    - Endowent - Industrial Corporation, 1930-1931 (Box 106, Folder 2481)
    - Equipping Radiology, 1916-l7 (Box 106, Folder 2482)
    - Executive Committee, 1922-1938 (Box 106, Folder 2483 - 2489)
    - Executive Committee, 1938-1940 (Box 107, Folder 2490 - 2491)
    - Financial, 1925-1940 (Box 107, Folder 2492)
    - Fitkin Memorial -Pavilion Dedication, 1930 (Box 107, Folder 2493)
    - Free Beds, 1918 (Box 107, Folder 2494)
    - General Hospital Society of Connecticut and, 1913 (Box 107, Folder 2495)
    - Yale University: Agreement - May 29, 1913, 1918 (Box 107, Folder 2496)
    - Gifford Fund, Executive Committee on Group Insurance, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 2497)
    - Health Insurance Plan, 1930-1931 (Box 107, Folder 2498)
    - History Rooom, 1918 (Box 107, Folder 2499)
    - Hospital and Medical School Relations, 1910-14 (Box 107, Folder 2500)
    - House Staff, 1938-1940 (Box 107, Folder 2501)
      - Affiliated with the Medical School, 1943 (Box 107, Folder 2502)
      - Assignments, 1937-1944 (Box 107, Folder 2503)
      - Assignments (incomplete), 1943-1944 (Box 107, Folder 2504)
      - Dinner, 1939 (Box 107, Folder 2505)
    - Indenture and Agreement between University, Hospital, and Dispensary, 1931 (Box 107, Folder 2506)
    - Intern Council, 1940 (Box 107, Folder 2507)
    - Isolation Pavilion, 1929-1930 (Box 107, Folder 2508)
    - Joint Committee with Yale Corporation, 1944 (Box 107, Folder 2509)
    - Laboratories, Reports on, 1940 (Box 107, Folder 2510)
    - Law Suit, 1930 (Box 107, Folder 2511)
    - Leprosy Cases, 1918 (Box 107, Folder 2512)
    - Litigation, 1930-1933 (Box 107, Folder 2513)
    - Medical Board, 1919-1935 (Box 107, Folder 2514 - 2516)
    - Medical Board, 1935-1940 (Box 108, Folder 2517 - 2521)
    - Medical Laboratory, 1927-1944 (Box 108, Folder 2522)
    - Medical School Relations, 1925-1926 (Box 108, Folder 2523)
    - Medical Staff Meetings, 1920-1922 (Box 108, Folder 2524)
    - New Haven' Hospital Fund, 1931-1932 (Box 108, Folder 2525)
    - Professional Fees, 1934-1940 (Box 108, Folder 2526 - 2527)
    - Public Relations, 1929-1934 (Box 108, Folder 2528)
    - Publicity, 1929-1934 (Box 108, Folder 2529)
    - Raleigh Fitkin Memorial and correspondence with A.E. Fitkih, 1929-1933 (Box 108, Folder 2530)
    - Rate Investigation Publicity, 1934 (Box 108, Folder 2531)
    - Record Boom Rules, 1931 (Box 108, Folder 2532)
    - Relations of New Haven Hospital to the General Hospital Situation in New Haven, 1929 (Box 108, Folder 2533)
    - Reports of Visitors, 1932-1933 (Box 108, Folder 2534)
    - Reports to (All departments ending Academic Year 1937) (Box 108, Folder 2535)
    - Reports to (All departments ending Academic Year 1938) (Box 108, Folder 2536)
    - Roster, undated (Box 108, Folder 2537)
    - Roster, 1930-1936 (Box 108, Folder 2538)
    - Statistics, 1930-1934 (Box 108, Folder 2539)
    - Social Service Program, 1930-1932 (Box 109, Folder 2540)
    - Superintendency: correspondence re: possible candidate, 1930-1938 (Box 109, Folder 2541)
    - Superintendent.
      - Buck, Albert W., 1926-1932 (Box 109, Folder 2542 - 2543)
      - Looking for a, 1922 (Box 109, Folder 2544)
      - Rappleye, Willard C., 1922-1925 (Box 109, Folder 2545)
      - Successor to Dr. Rapp1eye, 1925 (Box 109, Folder 2546)
    - Surgical Pavilion and Women's Pavilion, 1931-1932 (Box 109, Folder 2547)
    - Surgical Service, 1925-1926 (Box 109, Folder 2548)
    - Survey of Hospital by Dr. Winford Smith, 1918 (Box 109, Folder 2549)
    - Survey of Hospitals (proposed): Governor Trumbull, 1926 (Box 109, Folder 2550)
    - Survey: Teaching Hospitals with particular reference to New Haven Hospital, 1924 (Box 109, Folder 2551)
    - Theological STudents, Clinical Training of, 1935-1939 (Box 109, Folder 2552)
    - Tomkins Pavilion - Dedication, 1931-1932 (Box 109, Folder 2553)
    - Veneral Disease Clinic, 1918-19 (Box 109, Folder 2554)
    - Yale - New Haven Medical Center, 1938 (Box 109, Folder 2555)
  - Hospital, New Haven and William Wirt Winchester: Finances, 1937-1938 (Box 109, Folder 2556)
  - Hospital, Bridgeport: Cost of Hospitalization, 1931-1933 (Box 109, Folder 2557)
  - Hospital, Grace - New Haven Community, 1932-1951 (Box 109, Folder 2558)
    - Laboratory Organization (A. W. Snoke), 1947 (Box 109, Folder 2559)
    - Treasurer's office, 1948-1949 (Box 109, Folder 2560)
    - University Service, 1947-1948 (Box 109, Folder 2561)
  - Hospital, Hartford: Cost of Hospitalization, 1932-1933 (Box 110, Folder 2562)
  - Hospital, Indian School, Albuquerque, New Mexico, United Pueblos Agency: clinical clerkships, 1942-1943 (Box 110, Folder 2563 - 2564)
  - Hospital, Madras, undated (Box 110, Folder 2565)
  - Hospital, New York City Memorial, 1928-1929 (Box 110, Folder 2566)
  - Survey of, 1928-1929 (Box 110, Folder 2567)
  - Hospital, Psychiatric, 1923 (Box 110, Folder 2568)
    - Proposed: state in cooperation with Yale School of Medicine and Hospital, 1935-1938 (Box 110, Folder 2569)
  - Hospital, Psychopathic: Commission of 1922-State of Connecticut (Box 110, Folder 2570)
  - Hospital, United States Veterans (proposed), 1927-1929 (Box 110, Folder 2571 - 2572)
  - Hospital, Veterans Administration (Newington): Dean's Committee, 1948-1952 (Box 110, Folder 2573)
  - Hospital, Waterbury: cost of hospitalization, 1931-1932 (Box 110, Folder 2574)
  - Hospital~ William W. Badeus (Norwich), 1927 (Box 110, Folder 2575)
  - Hospital, William Wirt WInchester, 1932-1933 (Box 110, Folder 2576)
    - Correspondence with Mrs. Winchester and Dr. Wayland, 1915-19 (Box 110, Folder 2577)
    - Miscellaneous, 1926-1929 (Box 110, Folder 2578)
    - Reports, 1927-1934 (Box 110, Folder 2579)
    - Staff, 1915-19 (Box 110, Folder 2580)
    - Survey Report, 1939-1940 (Box 110, Folder 2581)
  - Hospitals
    - Administration, Lectures on, 1938 (Box 110, Folder 2582)
    - Cost of Medical Care Publicity, 1931-1932 (Box 110, Folder 2583)
    - Data, 1926-1927 (Box 110, Folder 2584)
    - Hospitalization Service Plan (students), 1938-1944 (Box 110, Folder 2585)
    - Training of Hospital Administrators, Conference on - sponsored by Rockefeller Foundation, 1920 (Box 110, Folder 2586)
  - Human Welfare Group, 1929-1931 (Box 111, Folder 2587)
    - Addresses by M.C. Winternitz, 1929-1932 (Box 111, Folder 2588 - 2589)
    - Addresses, requests for, 1926-1932 (Box 111, Folder 2590)
    - Berger, D. Spencer: responses to letter re:solicitation of funds, 1931 (Box 111, Folder 2591)
    - Bridgeport Luncheon, 1930 (Box 111, Folder 2592)
    - Buffalo Dinner, 1929-1930 (Box 111, Folder 2593)
    - Campaign, 1929-1930 (Box 111, Folder 2594)
    - Campaign Approaches, 1929-1931 (Box 111, Folder 2595 - 2597)
    - Campaign Approaches, 1931-1932 (Box 112, Folder 2598 - 2599)
    - Chicago Dinner, 1930 (Box 112, Folder 2600 - 2601)
    - Cincinnatti Dinner, 1930 (Box 112, Folder 2602)
    - Cleveland, 1930 (Box 112, Folder 2603)
    - Clinical Sociology, 1930 (Box 112, Folder 2604)
    - Community Health Center, 1931-1932 (Box 112, Folder 2605)
    - Connecticut Committee, 1929-1931 (Box 112, Folder 2606)
      - Luncheon, 1931 (Box 112, Folder 2607)
    - Contract (535)43 18082-E, 1943-1944 (Box 112, Folder 2608)
    - Corportaionts Committee on, 1929-1930 (Box 112, Folder 2609)
    - Detroit, 1929 (Box 112, Folder 2610)
    - Director's Committee Dtnner, 1931 (Box 112, Folder 2611)
    - Executive Committee, 1929-1931 (Box 113, Folder 2612 - 2613)
    - General, 1929-1932 (Box 113, Folder 2614)
    - Gifts to, 1931 (Box 113, Folder 2615)
    - Group Dinners, 1929-1930 (Box 113, Folder 2616)
    - Hartford Dinner, 1929 (Box 113, Folder 2617)
    - House Officers Dinner, 1933 (Box 113, Folder 2618)
    - Informatiop. Requests for, 1929-1931 (Box 113, Folder 2619)
    - Lists Committee, 1931 (Box 113, Folder 2620)
    - Milwaukee Dinner, 1929-1930 (Box 113, Folder 2621)
    - Minneapolis Dinner, 1930 (Box 113, Folder 2622)
    - National Advisory Committee
      - Acceptances and regrets re serving on Committee, 1929-1930 (Box 113, Folder 2623)
      - Connecticut Committee Endorsements, 1929-1931 (Box 113, Folder 2624)
      - Dinner, 1930 (Box 113, Folder 2625)
    - New Haven Hospital Fund, 1930-1932 (Box 113, Folder 2626)
    - New York Dinner, 1930 (Box 114, Folder 2627)
    - Pan-American Conference, 1931 (Box 114, Folder 2628)
    - Philadelphia Dinner, 1930 (Box 114, Folder 2629)
    - Publicity, Comments, 1929-1931 (Box 114, Folder 2630)
    - Publicity Material:. Mr. Lund, 1931-1932 (Box 114, Folder 2631)
    - Reports
      - Chemistry in Relation to Medicine, 1931 (Box 114, Folder 2632)
      - Child Care at the New Haven Hospital, 1932 (Box 114, Folder 2633)
      - Clinical Sociology, Plan for at Yale University, 1931 (Box 114, Folder 2634)
      - Fellows of the Institute, Memorandum, 1931 (Box 114, Folder 2635)
      - Group Dinners, 1930 (Box 114, Folder 2636)
      - Human Problems in Industry, 1930 (Box 114, Folder 2637)
      - Isolation Pavilion, 1929 (Box 114, Folder 2638)
      - A New Concept in Nursing, 1930 (Box 114, Folder 2639)
      - Positive Health, 1930 (Box 114, Folder 2640)
      - Purpose, Progress and Needs, 1931 (Box 114, Folder 2641)
      - Surgical Pavilion, 1929 (Box 114, Folder 2642)
      - Women's Pavilion, 1930 (Box 115, Folder 2643)
    - Saint Paul Dinner, 1930 February (Box 115, Folder 2644)
    - Special Gifts Committee Luncheons, 1931 (Box 115, Folder 2645 - 2649)
    - Speeches, 1929-1930 (Box 115, Folder 2650 - 2651)
    - Summary of Progress and Needs, 1930 (Box 115, Folder 2652)
    - Twentieth Century Fund, Application to, 1929-1934 (Box 115, Folder 2653)
    - Waterbury Dinner, 1929 November (Box 116, Folder 2654)
    - Winsted, Connecticut Luncheon, 1930 April (Box 116, Folder 2655)
      - Winternitz, 1929-1930 (Box 116, Folder 2656)
      - Yale Representatives Dinner, 1929 November (Box 116, Folder 2657 - 2658)
  - Hypothalmus Seminar - Physiology 124, 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 2659)
  - Infectious Disease Research Unit, 1945-1946 (Box 116, Folder 2660)
  - Influenza, 1919· (Box 116, Folder 2661)
  - Information Desk - Sterling - Brady, 1938 (Box 116, Folder 2662)
  - Institute of Human Relations, 1926-1930 (Box 116, Folder 2663 - 2666)
    - Addresses, 1929-1930 (Box 116, Folder 2667)
    - Agreement between I.H.R. and.Yale University Press, 1931 (Box 116, Folder 2668)
    - Appointments, 1930-1931 (Box 116, Folder 2669)
    - Approaches, 1929 (Box 116, Folder 2670)
    - Budgets, 1929-1935 (Box 117, Folder 2671)
    - Bulletin of, 1931-1932 (Box 117, Folder 2672)
    - Child Development Clinic, 1919-1941 (Box 117, Folder 2673 - 2682)
    - Committee on, 1931-1937 (Box 117, Folder 2683 - 2684)
    - Construction Program, 1928-1929 (Box 117, Folder 2685)
    - Dedication, 1931 (Box 118, Folder 2686)
    - Dedication Plans, 1931 (Box 118, Folder 2687)
    - E.E.G. Laboratories, 1941-1946 (Box 118, Folder 2688)
    - Eugenics, 1929 (Box 118, Folder 2689)
    - Executive Secretary, 1930-1934 (Box 118, Folder 2690 - 2691)
    - Expert Shop, 1932 (Box 118, Folder 2692)
    - Family Physician: Proposed Study, 1932-1934 (Box 118, Folder 2693)
    - Fellows of the Institute, 1930-1931 (Box 118, Folder 2694)
    - Information, requests for, 1929-1931 (Box 118, Folder 2695)
    - Letterhead Paper, undated (Box 118, Folder 2696)
    - Miscellaneous, 1929-1931 (Box 118, Folder 2697)
    - Organization, 1929-1935 (Box 118, Folder 2698)
    - Personnel Considered, 1929 (Box 118, Folder 2699)
    - Positions - Applications for, 1929-1931 (Box 118, Folder 2700)
    - Psychology, 1930-1931 (Box 118, Folder 2701)
    - Publicity, 1929-1931 (Box 118, Folder 2702)
    - Reports by, 1928-1929 (Box 118, Folder 2703)
    - Shop " Expert " (Instrument)., 1932-1935 (Box 118, Folder 2704)
    - Social Agencies, 1931 (Box 118, Folder 2705)
    - Speechesby Winternitz, 1929-1930 (Box 118, Folder 2706)
    - Studies proposed: Reports etc., 1929-1934 (Box 119a, Folder 2707 - 2708)
  - Intelligence Test, 1922-1932 (Box 119a, Folder 2709)
  - Inter-American Relations, 1940-1941 (Box 119a, Folder 2710)
  - Interne Year: General Correspondence, 1913-14 (Box 119a, Folder 2711)
  - Internes and Medical Students, 1946 (Box 119a, Folder 2712 - 2713)
    - Association of, 1946 (Box 119a, Folder 2714)
  - Internship Appointments, 1938-1945 (Box 119b, Folder 2715 - 2717)
    The materials are restricted until January 1, 2036 due to University policy.
    - Class of March 1946 (Box 119b, Folder 2718)
    - Class of June 1947 (Box 119b, Folder 2719)
    - Class of June 1948 (Box 119b, Folder 2720)
    - Class of June 1949 (Box 119b, Folder 2721)
    - Class of June 1950 (Box 119b, Folder 2722)
    - Class of June 1951 (Box 119b, Folder 2723)
    - Class of June 1952 (Box 119b, Folder 2724)
  - Internships
    - Correspondence, 1922-1942 (Box 119b, Folder 2725 - 2728)
    - General, 1911-1940 (Box 119b, Folder 2729)
    - Letters of Recommendation, 1935-1941 (Box 119b, Folder 2730)
    - National Interassociation, 1951-1952 (Box 119b, Folder 2731)
    - New Haven Hospital, 1929-1942 (Box 120a, Folder 2732 - 2735)
    - Opportunities, 1933-1940 (Box 120a, Folder 2736)
    - Recommendations of Medical Students for, 1936-1940 (Box 120a, Folder 2737)
  - Inventory, 1937 (Box 120b, Folder 2738)
  - Laboratory Fees, 1910-19 (Box 120b, Folder 2739)
    - Collection of, 1931 (Box 121, Folder 2740)
  - Laboratory Manual Revision, 1944 (Box 121, Folder 2741)
  - Laboratory, John B. Pierce, 1932-1933 (Box 121, Folder 2742)
  - Laboratory Schedule, 1941 (Box 121, Folder 2743)
  - Ladies Aid, 1936-1941 (Box 121, Folder 2744 - 2745)
  - Lecture and Course Schedule, 1943 (Box 121, Folder 2746)
  - Lecture Lab Demonstration Schedules, 1946 (Box 121, Folder 2747)
  - Lecture Schedules, 1937-1947 (Box 121, Folder 2748 - 2749)
  - Lectures, 1924-1945 (Box 121, Folder 2750)
  - Edgar Allen Memorial, 1945-1946 (Box 121, Folder 2751)
  - Harry Burr Ferris, 1933-1939 (Box 121, Folder 2752)
  - Silliman, H.E. memorial, 1938-1939 (Box 121, Folder 2753)
  - Lectures and Lecturers, 1921-1931 (Box 121, Folder 2754)
  - Lecturesas, Meetings, Conferences, 1936-1942 (Box 121, Folder 2755 - 2756)
  - Legal Documents, 1910-1928 (Box 121, Folder 2757)
  - Library, Yale University, 1919~34 (Box 121, Folder 2758)
  - Licensure, Medical, 1910-1946 (Box 121, Folder 2759 - 2762)
  - Listerine Tests at Yale, 19'30 (Box 121, Folder 2763)
  - Literature, Medical (Lists etc.), 1931-1934 (Box 121, Folder 2764)
  - Lockers: Brady and Sterling, 1936-1952 (Box 122, Folder 2765 - 2766)
  - Mail Service, 1919-1925 (Box 122, Folder 2767)
  - Mammalian Seminar, 1943 (Box 122, Folder 2768)
    - Physiology 124, 1939-1940 (Box 122, Folder 2769)
  - Massachusetts, Commonwealth of: Approving Authority for Colleges and Medical Schools, 1939-1944 (Box 122, Folder 2770)
  - Matriculation: Routine to be followed, 1936-1952 (Box 122, Folder 2771 - 2773)
  - Medical Affairs, Director of, 1949-1951 (Box 122, Folder 2774)
  - Medical Care, 1938-1939 (Box 122, Folder 2775)
  - Medical Practice, 1925 (Box 122, Folder 2776)
  - Medical School Directory, 1931-1938 (Box 122, Folder 2777)
  - Medical School: Facts concerning., 1922-1936 (Box 122, Folder 2778)
  - Medical Study Units
    - Adolescence, 1933-1941 (Box 122, Folder 2779 - 2782)
      - General Education Board, 1934-1939 (Box 122, Folder 2783)
    - Atypical Growth, 1935-1941 (Box 122, Folder 2784 - 2785)
      - Seminars, 1933-1951 (Box 123, Folder 2786 - 2789)
      - Tumor Clinic, 1933-1938 (Box 123, Folder 2790)
    - Cardiovascular, 1950-1951 (Box 123, Folder 2791)
    - Dental Study Unit, 1937-1938 (Box 123, Folder 2792)
    - Neurological [see also Neuroanatomy, Section on, and Anatomy, Department of]-., 1925-1939 (Box 123, Folder 2793 - 2796)
      - Committee, 1935-1936 (Box 123, Folder 2797)
    - Oral Pathology (Dental), 1930-1942 (Box 123, Folder 2798 - 2806)
    - Oral Pathology (Dental), 1937-1944 (Box 124, Folder 2807 - 2810)
      - Memoranda, 1933-1936 (Box 124, Folder 2811)
      - News releases and clippings, 1934-1935 (Box 124, Folder 2812)
      - Report, 1937 (Box 124, Folder 2813)
      - Surgery, Dental, 1939-1942 (Box 124, Folder 2814)
    - Rehabilitation, 1951 (Box 124, Folder 2815)
  - Memorabilia, 1928-1951 (Box 124, Folder 2816 - 2817)
  - Memoranda, 1932-1941 (Box 124, Folder 2818)
  - Microphotography, 1938 (Box 124, Folder 2819)
  - Microscope, electron, 1944 (Box 124, Folder 2820)
  - Microscopes, 1911-193 (Box 124, Folder 2821 - 2828)
  - Microscopes, 1944-1949 (Box 125, Folder 2829 - 2832)
    - Cost, net price, etc. of microscopes for sale, undated (Box 125, Folder 2833)
    - Loaned by former graduates, 1942-1943 (Box 125, Folder 2834)
    - Report of stolen microscopes, 1938-1939 (Box 125, Folder 2835 - 2838)